The press conference for the launch of
The Memory The Series.
Why do we not know about any of this?
Just walk away from the Dream!
It’s for the safety of the people around you.
If you want revenge so badly,take it out on yourself.
but it will cause trouble for people around you as well.
What are you going to do?
I came.
Now you guys can let him go.
Sky?
You just came? I heard that you’ve been calling for us.
I'll hurry and get you the money.
You already got me the money.
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
How's it been, trying to take your revenge?
Feeling any better?
It's not what you think, is it?
So...
I think…
You can stop running after me, and Mom now.
P’Sun,
you need to live your life.
Mom.
P’Sun!
Are you awake?
P’Sun, do you remember me?
I’m the person that you really adore, remember?
Sun!
Do you remember us?
Who am I?
My Manager.
You've been sleeping for weeks,
even though the surgery went well.
We're so very worried.
I’m so thankful for you that day.
If it wasn’t for you that save me,
I would…
You won’t.
Really,
everything that happened.
It came out of my own resentment.
Okay,
The fact that you survived is beyond good news.
Next time, don't do this again. I'm begging you.
Sky, can you put the bed upward?
You okay?
Alright?
TWO-O
has anyone heard about him?
Not yet.
Here you go!
You used to love this, didn't you?
P’Pong?
You can eat this
when you get better, alright?
Hey!
Let go.
Let go of it!
How did you even come?
Oh here, I’m representing Speed Express.
Before this,
when you were taking other people's shifts to help them,
it meant a lot to them.
But of course, you didn’t know that, right?
I didn't think it would matter to anyone.
It’s fine. It’s good that you’re awake.
Here.
These are your friends.
They pitched in to get these for you.
You have to eat it all.
And be careful of others, they might steal it.
Oh, hey!
Right, I'll head back first.
I will deliver them the good news that you’re awake.
I'll put it here.
Thank you.
Eat it all, okay?
You two better be careful!
I’m keeping both of my eyes on you.
What!?
What a crazy man!
Hey.
Who is this again?
I'm sorry,
but I think you came to the wrong room.
Oh, hi, uncle.
Sia?
Oh, this uncle is
the person who helped me when Sun passed out.
Thank you so much.
Since you two seem to know each other so well.
I’ll let you two be.
We should go eat.
Take care, alright?
Let’s go.
Wait up, Mr. Manager.
If you ever need someone for a male lead,
do not hesitate to call me, okay?
Why the heck would you sit up?
Didn’t you look that they nearly stabbed your gut out,
and you’re still acting tough?
How did you come?
Sia Jo, he called me.
He said that you might be in trouble.
Although I didn't believe him.
So I went to see it with my very own eyes.
Sia Jo from Alice?
That's right.
Sia Jo,
or that bastard from Alice is my pal.
We’re tight.
When we were younger,
we've been to bathhouses together,
but now
it looks like he has his own bathhouse now.
Confused?
He also used to call,
and fact check your story with me.
And after he knew
that you had to work your ass off to pay my debt,
he cried like an old looking freaking baby.
I don't know what the hell is wrong with him.
That bastard likes to act all dramatic.
So, I owe you again?
This one you didn’t ask for.
And I'm willing to help
so I don't count.
Thank you.
And when I passed out,
what happened?
Who are you?
Don't you remember your daddy's face, boy?
Finish him!
Hey!
Are you really in trouble?
And you?
Oh, you still look fine.
Looks like I still have time for something fun.
Beat the shit out of him!
Since when did you come back?
Are you angry?
The suicide scene,
now I get it.
Why you portrayed the scene that way.
What do you mean?
You put your life at risk,
even though I told you to only focus on yourself.
Thirty missed calls from me.
You didn’t answer my calls at all.
If you have to choose between death and me,
you would choose death without any hesitation, right?
I don't…
You feel guilty.
because you blamed yourself for your brother's
and mother's deaths.
Jay.
Jay!
Put the knife down!
We can talk.
Jay.
Jay, don’t.
No.
Jay, please.
Jay, don't.
Jay.
No, Jay.
Jay!
Jay, stop!
How do you feel now
to be the one who’s trying to kill me?
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
Ahh.
Two baht guy,
you’re looking for my Jay, right?
That guy has something to deal with.
The injury isn't serious.
so the doctor let him go since he’s quite stable.
Although the doctor referred him
to the psychiatric department
because they thought that he tried to kill himself.
So I told the doctor,
“Doctor, sir.
he only did that to get back at his boyfriend”
But the doctor insisted that he should be
cleared by a psychiatrist anyway.
He really needs a good therapist anyway.
You say nothing about the fact that
I call you his boyfriend,
so you…
are really becoming Mr. Three baht?
Huh?
Right?
Mr. Three baht
Hoo! Hoo! Hoo!
It’s not like that.
Whatever,
I'm sorry for my beloved nephew.
Sometimes he likes to be self-centered like a child.
But after this,
I need you to control his behavior.
I think…
You can do it, right?
Huh?
Good, good.
I'm glad that
you're not dead.
You're Mr. Three Baht.
That means you're family.
Family
needs to rely on each other.
You stay here.
I have to go.
Please take care of him for me.
Yes.
You didn’t have to lie to me.
I…
You want me to feel even more guilty?
Let’s go back to your room.
You’re invited to the meeting. Click the link below to join.
Hello, all of you.
Hello, sir.
Sit down, sit down, please.
Thank you so much.
Sorry to keep you all waiting.
We can start now.
Alright, I’m going to cut to the chase now.
Our company
has improved significantly over the past several years.
We are now the leading entertainment company in the country.
Even though what we still lack now is funding.
And that is the reason why Mr.Songpol is here with us today.
The chairman and the board members
have proposed a merger of the company.
Between Dream Entertainment and SPG
where the SPG will be a major investor.
They will increase the capital by three times
the company's market capitalization.
And we also would like to propose a name
change of the company to
SPDream for our unity.
It sounds good.
But why is it so sudden?
It's not sudden at all.
All propose is for the future of SPDream
which will grow to be the leader
in the industry globally.
Besides,
the board members demanded the removal of Director Arthur
from Dream Entertainment.
As you all know,
Director Arthur actions,
what he has done without consulting others.
His action has damaged the company gravely.
Yeah, he ruined many good deals that I've made.
And also his arrogant demeanor
has given the company bad publicity.
Not to mention that
he just signed off on tens of millions Baht
to approve that unknown indie woman director
on a random project.
You’re right.
I understand everyone's frustration,
so should we vote now?
Who will vote to dismiss him from the position?
Are you trying to fire me?
Sometimes Jay still has a mischievous side.
Have a look at this.
How did you know Jay?
I was a bodyguard for Jay's mother.
I had worked with her for the longest time.
I made a mistake that day.
Yes?
A parcel for Ms. Pavinee?
Yes, yes.
I only let you out of my sight for a second.
What!
No, what is happening to her?
Boss!
Miss Pavinee!
Jay and I met again at his mother's funeral.
You think you're so tough, don't you?
At first, it was just helping to vent the sadness.
But it turned out that I broke his right arm.
Oh, yeah.
So it's you who hurt it.
I’m too old now, my knees are hurting. I need my med now.
My knees feel weak.
Even if you want to fire me,
but I still own ten percent of this company.
So I’m still allowed to attend this meeting.
So now I'm going to propose
we should put the dismissal of Director Arthur
on hold for now.
If we talk about performance,
Director Arthur has always provided new connections for us.
Hasn’t he?
Our profits sink
due to his little projects.
So I don’t think his performance is that good.
We should talk about the numbers, Vice President.
If you want to talk about numbers,
I also have something to propose too.
This is not your place to do so anymore.
You're so naive.
As far as I know,
Dream is still growing nonstop,
but you're here acting like a child.
Who would want to waste time listening to you?
And actually,
now you're not involved in The Memory Project anymore.
But I’m just going to spare you the information that
we’re already done with the casting process,
and we already made deals with sponsors.
It's only a matter of when we'll start filming,
and it'll be soon.
Now, many countries have made deals to
buy the streaming rights.
Well,
you’ve done things very quickly and impressively.
I never thought you had already signed contracts
with other countries.
But is it really going that well?
You’re obviously visionless.
We’re about to start filming, and you’re asking this?
Well, that is as far as it can go.
What a stupid question.
Mr Songpol?
Actually no,
nobody in here has read that contract, right?
If you read it carefully, you wouldn’t dare fire me.
So, no one reviews the production list
that needs to be processed before filming, right?
In it, it’s clearly stated that
the series will have a song
that originally made for the series from beginning
to end of the series.
Did you guys have the rights to use that song?
The copyright of that song,
I'm the only one in the world who owns it.
I told you I’m not going to sell the copyright to Dream.
I didn't come as a representative from Dream.
Here.
I know you were promised a very unfair contract earlier.
They said your song
will not last very long.
And then it will become outdated.
But I believe your song will become a legendary song
that stay with us for a long time.
At first, I didn't think this song
would be worth that much.
Would you like to sell it to me?
You’re saying that I can add terms
to terminate the contract,
in case they don't use my original lyrics?
Yes, you should not be exploited twice.
Because you wrote it.
This right should be yours from the beginning.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
It's a pleasure.
Manhattan
You sold everything,
What would you do with that money?
I want to buy the copyright to a song.
Isn't it a little expensive?
If it’s the price of getting revenge,
then nothing is too expensive for me.
You are really your mother’s son.
Or to be clear,
I hold the public distribution rights
to the song for 10 years.
And I won't allow you to use it.
If based on the contract,
you guys have exactly ten years to produce this series.
Although if you breach the contract,
how much do you have to pay?
We don't need that song.
We can use other songs instead.
It’s just a song.
I don't need your permission for it.
I can just find someone to compose the song similarly,
or just compose a new one.
It’s not that hard.
Whew.
Then I have no other choice.
Besides suing for copyright infringement.
You know, right?
I don't care about the outcome of the court's decision.
But I'm sure that
I can just delay this case for a decade.
Of course, I can do it easily.
Check the contract with the copyright owner.
The contract states that
the content can only be edited
if it's approved by the writer.
And importantly,
the content that writers absolutely do not allow is
the lyrics used in the epigraph.
I highlighted for you all on page seven.
Where lyrics are adapted.
will be considered to have broken the contract,
the writer can cancel the contract immediately.
All fines and compensation
must make your head spin.
Entertainment industry
is highly risky.
You probably already have considered
this level of risk beforehand.
But when the damage is done,
it will have your name all over it.
Get him out of here.
Get his ass out of here!
Oh, about the motion to remove me.
you guys can continue discussing.
How many people have agreed to fire me?
No one?
I do have one motion that I’d like to propose,
I’m going to fire all of you.
You want to destroy this place?
You can’t do that.
Right! You just own a copyright to a song.
You don’t have that much power over us.
You think that you’re the owner of Dream or something?
Yes, Dream is mine.
I am the rightful owner of the company.
This must clearly be a sitcom joke.
If you’re going to fantasize, at least make it believable.
That's right.
I think with these symptoms,
you really need a therapist.
Fine.
Let's get back to the numbers.
So, I have the right to serve as the company's president with my 10% stake.
Combined with my mother's stake.
the total came out to be 61 percent.
Ms. Pavinee,
Is he really a son of…
I can assure you that
Mr. Arthur is the only son of Ms. Pavinee.
What!
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
So what if you’re her child?
Didn't Ms.Pavinee give all of her shares to Mr. Kongkiat?
So what?
Please.
Yes, sir.
But it was a wrongful transfer.
Hey!
Don't make things up.
Otherwise, I can sue you.
Why would my mother transfer her shares to you,
without any money coming to her account?
And the e-mail denying the sale of her shares
that my mother sent you,
have you ever read any of it?
Before her death,
my mother has a will.
By appointing me as the executor of the estate.
And you, my uncle
served as a witness.
This is the document
confirming that
Mr. Athip
holds the majority shareholder of Dream Entertainment.
Now it's time for payback.
He looks quite scary, right?
He’s really exactly like his mother.
If she’s still here,
she would be laughing
for the fact that Jay has shown you this.
This isn’t over yet.
I heard that your heart wasn't good.
Be careful of what you do.
Yes, sir.
I prepared everything for you.
You should leave now,
wait until things blow over, then come back.
Thank you very much.
Ouch!
Hurt.
That’s hurt.
Where does it hurt?
No fever.
Ouch!
What are you doing?
Go.
I’m in pain.
Do you still dare to take a knife for someone else
when I never gave you permission?
I should be able to do things with you,
Instead, I have to keep my hands off you.
It's all your fault.
I'm holding myself back too.
I really want to touch you.
Little bunny, don't change the subject.
And are you still
not going to answer my call?
Well, I won’t when I’m busy.
Fine, just answer your call from now?
Done!
You’re going to rip my wound open.
Don't take your eyes off me.
Hey!
Why are you stopping the car?
Sleep well, didn’t you?
I've been waiting to play with you for a while.
Go!
I’ve been expecting you.
At first, I wanted to use you to celebrate my victory.
But since,
you’re being like this.
Consider this your last day on earth.
Let me go!
Get off me!
I dare you to try shoving it in,
I’m going to bite the whole thing out.
Still being smart-mouthed, huh?
Here for being a smart-mouthed.
Have you ever heard of an electric eel?
This is a police officer.
This is my kingdom.
How could you break in?
I said put the weapon down.
How did you get in?
Let me go!
Get off me!
I told you to let me go!
Let me go!
Get up carefully.
Sit here.
This is you in the video, right?
Yes, sir.
Take your money back!
And stop messing with my life.
That's not enough.
You're not going to stop, are you?
How long are you going to keep holding a grudge against me?
What happened five years ago,
you've never felt ashamed, have you?
Why should I be ashamed?
The person to be ashamed of is you, isn't it?
As for the money,
I never wanted it in the first place.
Because it's dirty money.
It’s the money that you extorted from others.
And for the reason that your mother and brother are dead,
it has nothing to do with me.
Everything happened because of you.
You are a damn murderer.
Now that you are unemployed,
with no backer.
It might come in handy.
Do you think you won?
I only allow you this once.
And I’m telling you this.
I’m going take everything that belongs to you,
including Director Arthur.
Are you calling me?
We see each other again,
Director Arthur.
But I don't want to see you.
The only one I want to see
is this person here.
Why are you still looking?
If you’re uncomfortable seeing people in love
Then get the hell out of here.
This is my revenge,
but you’re the one who ends it.
What are you talking about?
Isn't this your plan from the beginning,
to use Director Arthur to your advantage.
I’m just wondering
why don't I feel happy at all?
And I don't think that I need you to help me.
I have to,
you bought me for the price of a thousand
and two baht.
Six months later
Hello to all the press,
and all the fans.
Before we get started,
please welcome, the director and the cast to the main stage.
Everyone,
this project was not created to compete with anyone,
ingrained gracefully in the memory of all of you.
The Memory The Series is ready.
We will make the world share this memory together.
Oh, I thought it wouldn't be able to be here in time.
The traffic jam is really jamming.
How are you?
Well, fine.
PEN-NUENG just got to be a presenter on a product,
of course, with my selling skills.
I'm good, right?
How lucky are you to have me as a manager?
You really like to give yourself compliments, do you?
So how is it? Audition for the male lead for the first time.
Even if you didn't get the role, you still got something out of it, didn't you?
It's fun.
Considered it an experience.
It's not easy, but the people around me
encourage me very well.
My manager, people in the company, and all the cast friends.
Why don't you just pull some strings
with the president, then?
I can't.
He doesn’t like to pull any strings for me.
Maybe he likes to keep you for himself.
What?
Ugh! Nothing.
Thank you.
You seem excited.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
My puppy, you look handsome today.
Of course,
I'm just that handsome every day.
Only you have never seen that side of me.
Let's take a picture.
Can I bother anyone to take a picture for us?
Thank you P’Sun.
Congratulations.
Truly, thank you.
Sorry to bother.
Thank you very much.
Take a picture for us, please.
Excuse me.
Oh! Pakin
1! 2! 3! Nice!
Congratulations.
I can't believe you can finish filming this.
Thank you
Thank you for what?
You have to thank them.
Your last nude pictures,
I’m going to keep it for now..
Once you’re famous,
I'm posting them.
It won't be long.
Wait, wait, wait.
When did that happen?
I won't bother you any longer.
Oh, teacher Phueng.
Hello.
It’s nothing, really.
How are you doing lately?
Let’s eat Mala today.
Yeah.
Of course, papaya salad it is.
When did you shoot them?
When?
Sun!
Hello.
How are you?
Do you have any time available for me?
I have some free time.
That's great.
I'm going to film another short movie soon.
I have a role that I think would suit you very well.
It’s the supporting male lead role.
Oh my god.
He’s free, very free.
Then we'll talk again soon.
Alright.
See you later.
Goodbye.
P’Kajorn
Yes?
I'll be right back.
Yeah, yeah.
How are you?
Fortunately, I'm not dead yet.
Actually,
I wanted to thank you for that night.
The police said that
someone sent the video and the location to them
I didn't do it for you.
I knew you'd say that.
But I want to thank you anyway.
And...
About Wave...
Wave?
Why?
After everything was exposed,
I couldn’t get a hold of him.
I thought he was probably running from the police.
Now I heard about him again,
he was overdosed on drugs.
What are you going to do?
Once I survived all that,
I realised that revenge no longer matters to me anymore.
Not as important as being alive, anyway.
Now that I think like that,
things are definitely do not feel as heavy anymore.
As for the rest,
we'll just have to keep pushing forward.
I’m sorry.
You don't need to apologize.
It's not your fault alone.
How?
Do it like this.
Right.
Go for it.
Hey, almost got it.
Are you sure?
One more time, please.
Next one say to bro, okay?
Okay.
Yo Bro!
Hey don’t.
Don’t use your Gen Z slang with elder.
Whisk
Bro! Bro means brother.
No, no, no.
Right, bro?
Yo Bro!
Excuse me
Oh, yeah.
Okay.
Can we take a photo with?
Can I get a photo with him? I'm a fan club.
Oh, okay.
I take a photo.
Okay.
One, two, three!
Sia Po’s calling!
Yes, Sia.
The debtor you sent me,
he can’t do anything for shit.
Well,
It never makes money to pay the debt on time.
Not only that but, last time
do you know what he asked me to do?
What is it?
Yeah, wait and see.
I will send you a link.
And then you prepare to press subscribe
and share, okay?
Hi my lords,
once you join my live, don’t forget to send me gifts.
And then you get to see something deeper
than you've ever seen.
Five years is the time that
I learned and tried to understand.
I still think about Bank.
The person who used to take my name.
Camera!
Are you guys ready?
If you are then,
Action!
Don't come in.
Don't come in just one by one.
Just all of you come in at the same time.
Good!
Stronger!
He could be another one of my identities
that still lives the same way.
He still can't even recognize his own mistakes.
I don't know how long it would take Bank to understand
because becoming a new person is hard.
But being self-aware is even harder.
Good luck to you.
Want to jump down?
If you want to jump,
I can help by pushing your back.
Do you want it?
No.
If you’re planning on doing that,
I’ll be the one to push you down first.
So that I can have freedom.
Freedom?
So you know,
the reason that you don’t have freedom?
It’s because all of you
is mine.
So what is the capital city of Lithuania?
You asked me that a long time ago,
still want the answer now?
So?
It’s Vilnius.
We'll be going there next week.
Huh?
So, this is your first trip abroad, huh?
I’m telling you
that it won’t be your last.
Do you want it?
I thought that you’d smoke again.
I want to,
but I’ve seen you quit smoking.
And now smoking alone becomes so boring.
Then go sell the cigarette for two baht to the new person.
Mr. Two baht,
there's only one of you.
My dummy as well,
there’s only you that can be my Dummy.